bearinsider.com 2019-06-21

# Bear Insider

BearInsider.com was created to provide a constructive community for sharing information, opinions, and life's experiences and is primarily intended for current students, former students, supporters, and fans of University of California and its athletic programs.

By accepting the User Agreement and Posting Policy below you agree to be a productive citizen of this community.

Considering the real-time nature of this discussion forum, it is impossible for us to review posts or confirm the validity of information posted. Please remember that we at BearInsider.com do not actively monitor the contents of and are not responsible for any messages posted. We do not vouch for or warrant the accuracy, completeness or usefulness of any message, and are not responsible for the contents of any message. The messages express the views of the author of the message, not necessarily the views of this discussion forum or any entity associated with this discussion. Any user who feels that a posted message is objectionable is encouraged to contact us immediately by email. We have the ability to remove objectionable messages and we will make every effort to do so, within a reasonable time frame, if we determine that removal is necessary. This is a manual process, however, so please realize that we may not be able to remove or edit particular messages immediately.

Although Bear Insider does not and cannot review the messages posted and is not responsible for the content of any of these messages, we at Bear Insider reserve the right to delete any message for any or no reason whatsoever. You remain solely responsible for the content of your messages, and you agree to indemnify and hold harmless this BearInsider.com and their agents with respect to any claim based upon transmission of your message(s).

We at Bear Insider also reserve the right to reveal your identity (or whatever information we know about you) in the event of a complaint or legal action arising from any message posted by you.

Bear Insider reserves the right to revoke posting privileges of an individual for any or no reason at all. You agree that posting in this forum is a privilege and not a right. You will also agree not to take legal action against Bear Insider by your participation in this forum.

You agree that you are over the age of 13.

##  **POSTING POLICY**

 **  
**Posting on the forums

You agree, through your use of this service, that you will not use this forum to post any material which is knowingly:

  1. False and/or defamatory
  2. Inaccurate
  3. Abusive
  4. Vulgar
  5. Hateful
  6. Harassing
  7. Obscene
  8. Profane
  9. Sexually oriented
  10. Threatening
  11. Invasive of a person's privacy
  12. Thread Hijacking (knowingly redirecting the subject of a thread)
  13. Post padding (posting for the sole purpose of increasing post count)
  14. Trolling (posting to purposefully antagonize other posters)
  15. An attempt to get around the profanity filter
  16. Removal of moderator/staff edits from post
  17. Otherwise in violation of any law

When a post is found to contain any of the above violations that post is subject to removal and the poster is subject to further action (See Moderator Actions).

Revealing personal information about others will not be tolerated. Bear Insider has a zero tolerance policy for anyone who posts private or defamatory information on this forum without the consent of the parties involved. This includes, but is not limited to, posters on this forum, athletes/staff/officials of University of California, business owners etc.

 **Moderator actions**  
The forums at Bear Insider are moderated because we feel that it is necessary to maintain the health of this community. The moderators at Bear Insider have the ability to do a combination of three things when reacting to a post or other user action on the site. The moderator can:

  * Remove or edit the post.
  * Warn the user that a post or subject has violated the User Agreement and Posting Policy.
  * The poster may have their posting privileges suspended for 1 hour, 3 hours, 12 hours, 1 day, 3 days, 1 week, 2 weeks, 4 weeks, or permanently. The length of the suspension is determined by the severity of the action, and/or the user’s moderation history.

Posters that have been frequently moderated may be subject to longer suspensions per occurrence. Moderation questions are to be directed through our contact page. Please allow 48 hours for a response.  
 **  
Voting functions**  
The moderators of Bear Insider take the voting function seriously. The intent of the voting function is to draw moderator attention to a thread or post for review. If it is determined that the thread or post is in violation of our posting policy moderation action will be taken. However, if it is determined that the thread or post is not in violation of our posting policy the votes will be removed and the thread or post will remain. We encourage all users to take advantage of our voting function. It is our most reliable tool in maintaining the health of this community.

In the event that a post has remained up beyond a reasonable amount of time, correspondence is to be directed through our contact page to inform us of the thread in question. A link to the thread is helpful in expediting the review process.

 **Personal Attacks**  
Bear Insider will not tolerate hateful speech, degrading remarks, or personal attacks made about other posters, athletes/coaches/faculty at University of California, or anyone else.

Due to the size, scope and diversity of this forum, subjects that elicit differing opinions and passionate beliefs will undoubtedly be posted. Please remember that everyone is entitled to their own opinion. Refrain from attacking users in a malicious manner because their opinions and remember to direct your disagreement at a poster’s argument and not at the poster as a person. Many good threads have been derailed in the past because they have devolved from constructive debate into name calling.

Criticisms of coaches or administrators at University of California needs to be kept to their official capacities as coach or administrator. Attacking these individuals personally is not an appropriate discourse on this forum. This includes calling for the firing of a coach or administrator. In no way does this mean that we agree with the performance of a coach, or are hedging our alignment with a coaching staff or athletic department.

 **Posting pictures and hyperlinks**  
All images need to be work safe. This means no nudity, partial nudity, or pornographic images will be allowed on the site. All posts of this nature will be removed as soon as possible, and will result in an immediate suspension from the forums. 

Anything hyperlinked on the Bear Insider forum that is directed to a site with inappropriate material will be considered by our moderators as being posted directly onto our forums. If you link to a site that has inappropriate content you can be suspended per our posting policies.

 **Premium content**  
Content published in any of the Bear Insider premium forums is not to be posted on any other Bear Insider forum, or other sites on the internet. Users found to be posting premium content from Bear Insider may be subject to a suspension.

Premium material being shared on the other forums is not permitted. You have paid for the right to participate in those forums, but that does not mean you’re permitted to share that information with anyone you please.

We also ask that our users refrain from posting premium content on Bear Insider from other sites as well. Users found to be posting premium content from other sites may be subject to a suspension.

 **Usernames**  
Each person is entitled to one username per email account. Users found to have numerous “sock puppets” will face moderator action and possible loss of posting privileges. Usernames found to be inappropriate by Bear Insider will be suspended, and the account holder will need to contact customer support for renaming the user account and reinstatement of posting privileges.

Using a “sockpuppet” to get around a suspension will result in a ban for the sockpuppet account, and a lengthened suspension for the original account.

Accounts may not be shared. If an account is found to be shared among more than one person, an indefinite suspension will be placed on the account until the user contacts customer support.

Usernames cannot directly reflect the name of a business or organization that is not a current advertiser without explicit, prior permission from Bear Insider.

A username may be changed with good reason and at a reasonable frequency by emailing customer support. Provide the username you wish to change, the email address on the account, and a brief reason as to why you wish to change the username.

 **Advertisements**  
Please note that advertisements (including promotion of other sites on the Internet), chain letters, pyramid schemes, and solicitations will not be tolerated on this forum. This includes forum postings, links, signature lines and private messages. The only posters who are permitted to function in this way have been pre-approved by the administrators at Bear Insider as paying advertisers.

If a service is requested by a poster on the forums it is permissible to give contact information in response to that specific request.

If you are interested in advertising on Bear Insider please contact us.

 **Copyrighted material**  
You agree not to post any copyrighted material unless the copyright is owned by you or by Bear Insider. If it is learned/suspected that copyrighted material has been posted on Bear Insider by a user, the following steps will be taken:The copyrighted material will be removed via either the deletion or edit of the post in which it is contained.

  1. The incident will be logged in order to track repeated violations by a given user.
  2. The material should be republished only if said material is confirmed to NOT be in violation of a copyright.
  3. The user will be contacted and informed not to post copyrighted material.
  4. Repeat offenders will be banned from further postings.

When posting an article on Bear Insider we would ask that you don’t simply copy and paste the entire article onto our site. Simply post an excerpt of what the article is about, and then link to the original article.  
 **  
**

##  **CANCELLATION & REFUND POLICY**

All subscription sales are final. 

To cancel the auto-renewal of a subscription prior to the renewal date, log in to Bear Insider, select _Settings_ from the top-right menu, select _Cancel Auto-Renew_ , confirm the action by selecting _Yes_.

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally Identifiable Information' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.  

 **What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, credit card information or other details to help you with your experience.

 **  
When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or enter information on our site.

 **  
How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  *  ****To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
  *  ****To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
  *  ****To quickly process your transactions.
  *  ****To send periodic emails regarding your order or other products and services.
  *  ****To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

 **How do we protect your information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

We do not use Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. 

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

 **Do we use 'cookies'?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

  *  ****Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.
  *  ****Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.
  *  ****Keep track of advertisements.
  * Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.  

 **If users disable cookies in their browser:**

If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled and some of the features that make your site experience more efficient may not function properly.  

 **Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when it's release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety. 

However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Third-party links**

We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.

 **  
Google**

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en 

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.  

 **We have implemented the following:**

  *  ****Remarketing with Google AdSense
  *  ****DoubleClick Platform Integration

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website. 

**Opting out:  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.**

California Online Privacy Protection Act

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law's reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf

According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:  

Users can visit our site anonymously.

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.  

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word 'Privacy' and can be easily be found on the page specified above.

You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes: On our Privacy Policy Page  

Can change your personal information: By logging in to your account

How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?  

We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place. 

Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?  

It's also important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking

COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur: We will notify you via email within 7 business days

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

 **CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to:

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions
  * Process orders and to send information and updates pertaining to orders.
  * Send you additional information related to your product and/or service
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:

  *  Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  *  Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  *  Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  *  Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  *  Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  *  Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at support@f5sports.com or follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

 **Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.

BearInsider.com

addess 

city, state zip

email@BearInsider.com

phone

Bear Insider also reserves the right to change this notice at any time.

User Agreement modified 

.
